

GUIDO CALCIANO

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I've been working with human groups and teams of professionals for the last 10 years, always giving everything from myself to exceed at the task. Recently I've taken my first steps into IT, and I'm excited to keep on studying, learning and improving every day. I'm reliable and responsible, adaptable and great at teamwork. I'm currently looking for opportunities to develop my full potential and bring my aptitudes for an exciting new project!

PROJECTS

- Portfolio https://guidocalciano.com.ar
- Photography Website: HTML5, CSS, Javascript y Bootstrap.
- Road Trip Simulator: Text-based adventure game. Currently in development with Python. Play it!

CONTACT

- (+549) 11 5732 4784
- O CABA, Buenos Aires, Argentina
- () /guidocano
- in /guidocalciano

EDUCATION

REACT JS.

Coderhouse. Jan 2022 - In progress.

Including React JS, Node JS, Javascript, ES6, data flow, Firebase, SPA applications, among others.

CODO A CODO 4.0 - FULLSTACK PYTHON.

Buenos Aires City Goverment. Aug 2021 - Dec 2021.

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, Bootstrap, Diseño Web, Vue, MySQL, Flask, among others. Learnt how to fluently use different programming languages and the ability to fully develop a Website.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY.

Buenos Aires University. Mar 2006 - Dec 2012.

During my bachelor's Degree I acquired a practical but complex understanding of different problems and situations. As well as the capability to listen and to understand different points of view, allowing me to arrive to consense.

EXPERIENCE

SPECIAL EDUCATION TEACHER.

Adeei. Mar 2018 - Dec 2021.

Working with children and teenagers I developed my ability to learn, communicate and teach in an easy and didactic way. I worked in collaboration with other professionals to achieve the best interest for each student.

PARLIAMENTARY ASSISTANT.

Buenos Aires City Legislature. Jan 2016 - Dec 2017.

In this job I learnt to be efficient and responsible, working under pressure, problem solving, organization of events and schedule, communication between different areas.

SKILLS

TECHNOLOGIES

- PYTHON
- JAVASCRIPT
- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- MYSQL

LANGUAGES

- SPANISH: native.
- ENGLISH: bilingual. CEFR level: C1 (IELTS)

SOFT SKILLS

PROBLEM-SOLVER CREATIVITY ADAPTABILITY TEAMWORK

RESPONSABILITY AND COMMITMENT CRITICAL THINKING

OPEN-MINDEDNESS COMMUNICATION SELF-MOTIVATION